<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Greek geek</title>
    <link>https://lecromee.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Greek geek</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:28:19 +0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lecromee.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring inner workings of a random free android VPN</title>
      <link>https://lecromee.github.io/posts/bd_net_vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 03:28:19 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lecromee.github.io/posts/bd_net_vpn/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Nothing special here. Got some free time to play around and decided to explore a free VPN from android play store in hopes to find something interesting, solve some riddle and just have fun. For this experiment I chose &amp;ldquo;BD NET VPN&amp;rdquo;. It is freely avaible for any android phone from Google play store: BD NET VPN. There is nothing special in it. My interest grabbed that it was loading it encrypted configuration stored in github and I have experience finding interesting apps that use this method (not this time though).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swing VPN app is a DDOS botnet</title>
      <link>https://lecromee.github.io/posts/swing_vpn_ddosing_sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 03:28:19 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lecromee.github.io/posts/swing_vpn_ddosing_sites/</guid>
      <description>tldr: Swing VPN is using its user base to DDOS sites using its users as a an attack botnet.&#xA;Introduction It all started with a friend of mine complaining that his phone was doing a request to a specific app every few seconds. Initial assumption was that the phone was infected with a virus but a 2 minute investigation showed that all requests went from &amp;lsquo;Swing VPN&amp;rsquo; app which were legitimately installed on the phone as VPN service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Init</title>
      <link>https://lecromee.github.io/posts/init/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 03:27:59 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lecromee.github.io/posts/init/</guid>
      <description>About me Hello I do like doing crazy experiments and testing new stuff.&#xA;Mail: Click to show email In case you like math, here are my favorite numbers.&#xA;Bitcoin: 19ELnxocZnqwjUipL8jmMsF78BxWnypRP&#xA;Etherium: abc002968B6576cf2391fddE3EFC3d10D78bFd56</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
